[{"answer": "I didn't say you killed her.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is the matter with you?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I had many reactions.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What was your reaction to the interview?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I believed him.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Did you believe him?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I think -- I think she burned men all across America.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What did you think, by the end, was the most likely theory for how she died?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think the police behaved inappropriately?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, the cases were filed differently.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Why was he treated differently?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "When you dealt with him, did you question his sanity at all?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "No, it can't get any worse.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "It doesn't get worse than that, does it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "He allowed a load more kids to get abused, didn't he?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, they should be civilly liable and they are gong to be civilly liable.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "What should happen to them?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I think -- I think it's ridiculous.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, I have great respect for Tom Mesereau.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well, it's heartbreaking to say the least.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What do you make of it all, now that we know the lurid detail?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely, \"The Newsroom,\" which is on HBO, are -- is terrific.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "What do you make of the series so far?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, this is what they've done so wonderfully.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "And how realistic is that premise for a modern cable news network do you think?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "He has a point.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Is he right?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I think that on the one hand he should have been there.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "So does it matter that he didn't go to that convention?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Just a bad decision.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Is that right, though?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "This is a very respectful audience.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "He got booed for the phrase or because actually a lot of people in the audience like Obamacare or whatever you want to call it?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "It smacks of Ross Perot some years ago referring to black folk as you people.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Tavis, what did you make of that?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "EST: I think given the narrowness of the political system and the truncated options that most Americans have, there's no doubt that Barack Obama is better than Mitt Romney.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "That maybe he has learned some lessons about leadership and how to take on the Republicans?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I think Tom Mesereau was right earlier in this program.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I was glad to see the show.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Cornel?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Hey, how are you, how's it going?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, yes, America is still the great country of opportunity and look at what happened to me.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "What do you think about the current debates in America with regard to immigration, with regard to the American nationality, if you like?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "I mean I love Obama.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "Or do you think there's other work still to be done?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Does s it worry you if they are perhaps to take control, come November?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, America has changed a lot.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "And do they need to evolve with that change?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Yes, missile, hostile.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Yes, sloth sounds better, I think, don't you?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "I love them.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "Do you like doing the \"Ice Age\" movies?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "And he said that sloths store food in their cheek pouches and they're so slow and they chew so slow that it ferments and it becomes alcohol and they get drunk and they fall off the trees.", "docId": "120712pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 804}]